I Am: Celine Dion is a documentary, music film directed by Irene Taylor.
A raw and honest behind-the-scenes look at the iconic
superstar's struggle with a life-altering illness.
Serving as a love letter to her fans, this inspirational documentary highlights the music that
has guided her life while also showcasing the resilience of the human spirit.
Self, played by Céline Dion.
Self, played by Nelson Angélil.
Self, played by Eddy Angélil.
Self, played by Natalie Hamel-Roy.
Self (archive footage), played by René Angélil.
Self (archive footage), played by René-Charles Angélil.
I Am: Celine Dion is a 2024 American documentary film directed by Irene
Taylor, which centers around Canadian singer Celine Dion.
The film details Dion's life, career accomplishments
and battle with stiff-person syndrome.
It premiered in New York City on 17 June 2024 and was given a limited
theatrical release on 21 June 2024 by Amazon MGM Studios.
It became available for streaming on 25 June 2024, on Amazon Prime Video.
In Francophone countries, the film was titled Je suis: Céline Dion.
It received rave reviews from critics, who called it a raw and honest behind-the-scenes
look at the iconic superstar's struggle with a life-altering illness.
The documentary became the number one movie on Amazon Prime Video worldwide.
It also became Prime Video's all-time most popular documentary.
The I Am: Celine Dion soundtrack was released on 21 June 2024.
The film explores themes of love letter, behind the scenes,
illness, singer-songwriter, power of love.